# Amelia Goodson

## Web Developer

Inquisitive and driven web developer with a flair for design and thirst for knowledge. Experienced in working with teams to produce digital content that engages customers and delivers conversions. Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React, I enjoy creating functional, accessible and responsive websites from the initial wireframing to deployment.

## **Professional Experience**

### Communications & Policy Assistant, Landcom

Sydney (February 2018 – January 2022) Responsibilities:

- Maintained corporate website using WordPress content management system and associated plugins.
- Organised large-scale conference of government leaders, including venues, designing the agenda and theme, soliciting speakers and making travel arrangements.
- Verified factual content of the Annual Report, which involved fact-checking hundreds of statements via research and consultation.
- Wrote compliments and complaints policy and managed the accompanying reporting system, periodically conducting internal training on the policy and process.
- Managed departmental budgets and acted as first point of call for advice on procurement.

#### **Executive Assistant, Corporate Finance, Ashurst**

London (December 2015 – September 2017) Responsibilities:

- Performed billable legal work including drafting share pledges, account pledges and facility agreements;
- Drafted submissions to the Board in regards to post-Brexit implications for the business;
- Managed expenses including credit card reconciliation and expense reimbursement; and
- Provided high-level administrative and legal support to four senior associates and one senior partner by amending legal documents, organising travel and managing diaries.

## **Executive Assistant, Commercial Disputes, Herbert Smith Freehills**

Sydney (February 2012 - September 2014) Responsibilities:

- Supported partners and associates in areas of complex commercial litigation and transactions.
- Managed monthly billing of over \$1 million to high-profile clients.
- Prepared case summaries and detailed evidence

### **Contact**

**Phone** 

0478 097 895

**Email** 

ameliajanegoodson@gmail.com

### **Skills**

**HTML** 

**CSS** 

**JavaScript** 

jQuery

React

**Node** 

**Responsive Design** 

**UX & UI Design** 

- chronologies.
- Handled office scheduling and made notes for deadlines, motions and other important dates.
- Completed document revisions, court document filings, travel arrangements and client billing.

### Legal Secretary, Workers Compensation, DLA Piper

Sydney (February 2010 - January 2012) Responsibilities:

- Provided paralegal support for one high volume fee-earner, managing over 400 files;
- Reviewed insurance, surveillance and medical reports to assess claims and damages;
- Liaised with clients regarding complex workers compensation matters; and
- Drafted documents including affidavits, depositions, letters of demand and briefs to counsel.

### **Education**

2021-07 - 2021-10	IT Support Professional Certificate
2021 10	Google
2020-01 - 2020-07	Full-Stack Web Development Certificate
,	University Of Sydney & Trilogy
2019-11 - 2020-01	Fundamentals Of Digital Marketing Short Course
2020 02	Google Digital Garage
2017-01 - 2020-06	Bachelor Of Laws (First Class Hons)
2020 00	University Of New England Thesis topic: Examining liability frameworks to accommodate injuries resulting from Al in healthcare.
2013-01 - 2015-10	<b>Diploma Of Business</b> <i>TAFE NSW</i> Award for Most Outstanding Student
2006	Higher School Certificate
	St Mary's Senior High School

UAI score: 98.55. Premier 's Award and Award for Most Outstanding Student